-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rayne_Longboards

Rayne	B-ORG	X
Longboards	I-ORG	X
was	O
established	O
in	O
2004	O
by	O
owner	O
and	O
operator	O
Graham	B-PER
Buksa	I-PER
.	O

He	O
began	O
by	O
producing	O
longboard	O
decks	O
at	O
their	O
factory	O
located	O
in	O
North	B-LOC
Vancouver	I-LOC
,	O
British	B-LOC
Columbia	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
business	O
later	O
expanded	O
to	O
produce	O
a	O
range	O
of	O
products	O
including	O
skateboards	O
,	O
longboards	O
,	O
snowskates	O
and	O
powsurfers	O
.	O

In	O
2008	O
,	O
Rayne	B-ORG	X
developed	O
a	O
manufacturing	O
system	O
for	O
producing	O
boards	O
entirely	O
from	O
bamboo	O
and	O
fibreglass	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
strength	O
to	O
weight	O
ratio	O
,	O
are	O
more	O
water	O
resistant	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
their	O
flex	O
longer	O
than	O
traditional	O
maple	O
made	O
boards	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Automattic

On	O
January	O
11	O
,	O
2006	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
announced	O
that	O
Toni	B-PER
Schneider	I-PER
would	O
be	O
leaving	O
Yahoo!	B-ORG
to	O
become	O
CEO	O
of	O
Automattic	B-ORG	X
.	O

He	O
was	O
previously	O
CEO	O
of	O
Oddpost	B-ORG
before	O
it	O
was	O
acquired	O
by	O
Yahoo!	B-ORG
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
continued	O
as	O
a	O
senior	O
executive	O
.	O

In	O
April	O
2006	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
revealed	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
Regulation	O
D	O
filing	O
,	O
that	O
Automattic	B-ORG	X
raised	O
approximately	O
$1.1	O
million	O
in	O
funding	O
,	O
which	O
Mullenweg	B-PER
addressed	O
in	O
his	O
blog	O
.	O

Investors	O
were	O
Polaris	B-ORG
Ventures	I-ORG
,	O
True	B-ORG
Ventures	I-ORG
,	O
Radar	B-ORG
Partners	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
CNET	B-ORG
.	O

On	O
September	O
23	O
,	O
2008	O
,	O
Automattic	B-ORG	X
announced	O
acquiring	O
IntenseDebate	B-ORG
.	O

Simplenote	O
–	O
note	O
-	O
taking	O
and	O
sync	O
service	O
based	O
on	O
another	O
Automattic	B-ORG	X
project	O
simperium.com	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hurricane_Camille

Emerging	O
into	O
the	O
Gulf	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Mexico	B-LOC
,	O
Camille	O	X
underwent	O
another	O
period	O
of	O
rapid	O
intensification	O
and	O
became	O
a	O
Category	O
5	O
hurricane	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
as	O
it	O
moved	O
northward	O
towards	O
the	O
Louisiana	B-LOC
–	I-LOC
Mississippi	I-LOC
region	O
.	O

Despite	O
weakening	O
slightly	O
on	O
August	O
17	O
,	O
the	O
hurricane	O
quickly	O
re-intensified	O
back	O
into	O
a	O
Category	O
5	O
hurricane	O
before	O
it	O
made	O
landfall	O
in	O
Pass	B-LOC
Christian	I-LOC
,	O
Mississippi	B-LOC
,	O
early	O
on	O
August	O
18	O
,	O
at	O
peak	O
intensity	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
minimum	O
pressure	O
of	O
900	O
mbar	O
(	O
26.58	O
inHg	O
)	O
.	O

This	O
was	O
the	O
second-lowest	O
pressure	O
recorded	O
for	O
a	O
US	B-LOC
landfall	O
.	O

Only	O
the	O
1935	O
Labor	O
Day	O
hurricane	O
had	O
a	O
lower	O
pressure	O
at	O
landfall	O
.	O

As	O
Camille	O	X
pushed	O
inland	O
,	O
it	O
quickly	O
weakened	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
tropical	O
depression	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
Ohio	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
.	O

Once	O
it	O
emerged	O
offshore	O
,	O
Camille	O	X
was	O
able	O
to	O
restrengthen	O
to	O
a	O
strong	O
tropical	O
storm	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
became	O
extratropical	O
on	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
Camille	O	X
was	O
subsequently	O
absorbed	O
by	O
a	O
frontal	O
storm	O
over	O
the	O
North	B-LOC
Atlantic	I-LOC
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O

Camille	O	X
caused	O
tremendous	O
damage	O
in	O
its	O
wake	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
produced	O
a	O
peak	O
official	O
storm	O
surge	O
of	O
24	O
feet	O
(	O
7.3	O
m	O
)	O
.	O

The	O
hurricane	O
flattened	O
nearly	O
everything	O
along	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
state	O
of	O
Mississippi	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
caused	O
additional	O
flooding	O
and	O
deaths	O
inland	O
while	O
crossing	O
the	O
Appalachian	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
of	O
Virginia	B-LOC
.	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
Camille	O	X
killed	O
259	O
people	O
and	O
caused	O
$1.43	O
billion	O
in	O
damages	O
(	O
equivalent	O
to	O
$9.8	O
billion	O
in	O
2018	O
)	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Andrew_Fotiadis

Panos	B-PER	X
Andrew	I-PER	X
Andy	I-PER	X
Fotiadis	I-PER	X
is	O
an	O
English	O
former	O
footballer	O
of	O
Greek	O
descent	O
,	O
best	O
known	O
for	O
his	O
time	O
at	O
Luton	B-LOC
Town	I-LOC
.	O

Fotiadis	B-PER	X
started	O
the	O
2000	O
–	O
01	O
campaign	O
in	O
the	O
starting	O
lineup	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
some	O
fine	O
form	O
.	O

He	O
won	O
caps	O
for	O
the	O
England	B-LOC
under	O
-	O
15	O
and	O
under	O
-	O
18	O
teams	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Dynamo_Dresden_players

As	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
leading	O
clubs	O
in	O
East	B-LOC
Germany	I-LOC
,	O
Dynamo	B-ORG	X
Dresden	I-ORG	X
provided	O
36	O
East	B-LOC
German	I-LOC
internationals	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
country	O
's	O
second	O
most-capped	O
player	O
,	O
Hans-Jürgen	B-PER
Dörner	I-PPER
,	O
and	O
its	O
joint	O
second	O
top	O
scorer	O
,	O
Hans-Jürgen	B-PER
Kreische	I-PER
.	O

Kreische	B-PER
and	O
Siegmar	B-PER
Wätzlich	I-PER
were	O
in	O
East	B-LOC
Germany	I-LOC
's	O
squad	O
for	O
their	O
only	O
World	O
Cup	O
appearance	O
(	O
1974	O
)	O
,	O
while	O
twelve	O
Dynamo	B-ORG	X
players	O
won	O
Olympic	O
medals	O
,	O
including	O
six	O
gold	O
medallists	O
in	O
1976	O
.	O

After	O
German	O
reunification	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
Dynamo	B-ORG	X
players	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
represent	O
the	O
Germany	B-LOC
national	O
team	O
,	O
including	O
Jens	B-PER
Jeremies	I-PER
,	O
Ulf	B-PER
Kirsten	I-PER
,	O
Olaf	B-PER
Marschall	I-PER
and	O
Alexander	B-PER
Zickler	I-PER
.	O

Dynamo	B-ORG	X
have	O
also	O
seen	O
internationals	O
from	O
other	O
nations	O
,	O
including	O
Australia	B-LOC
(	O
Joshua	B-PER
Kennedy	I-PER
and	O
Mark	B-PER
Schwarzer	I-PER
)	O
,	O
the	O
Czech	B-LOC
Republic	I-LOC
(	O
Ivo	B-PER
Ulich	I-PER
and	O
Tomas	B-PER
Votava	I-PER
)	O
,	O
Slovenia	B-LOC
(	O
Klemen	B-PER
Lavrič	I-PER
and	O
Miran	B-PER
Pavlin	I-PER
)	O
and	O
Sweden	B-LOC
(	O
Johnny	B-PER
Ekström	I-PER
)	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Diana_(1823)

Diana	O	X
was	O
a	O
steam	O
paddle	O
steamer	O
built	O
in	O
1823	O
as	O
a	O
merchant	O
vessel	O
and	O
purchased	O
by	O
the	O
Bengal	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG
in	O
1824	O
.	O

During	O
the	O
First	O
Anglo-Burmese	O
War	O
she	O
became	O
the	O
first	O
steam-powered	O
warship	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	B-ORG
East	I-ORG
India	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
to	O
see	O
action	O
.	O

The	O
war	O
ended	O
on	O
8	O
March	O
1826	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
year	O
she	O
was	O
transferred	O
to	O
the	O
Burmese	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG
.	O

Although	O
one	O
reference	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
broken	O
up	O
in	O
1836	O
,	O
most	O
assert	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Singapore	B-LOC
.	O

Diana	O	X
steamed	O
to	O
Singapore	B-LOC
on	O
28	O
February	O
1836	O
.	O

Johnston	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	I-ORG
advertised	O
her	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O

The	O
East	B-ORG
India	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
purchased	O
her	O
in	O
March	O
1837	O
and	O
appointed	O
Samuel	B-PER
Congalton	I-PER
her	O
captain	O
.	O

Diana	O	X
's	O
establishment	O
consisted	O
of	O
her	O
captain	O
,	O
two	O
European	O
officers	O
and	O
thirty	O
Malays	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
East	B-ORG
India	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
's	O
service	O
Diana	O	X
suppressed	O
piracy	O
and	O
conducted	O
maritime	O
surveys	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Java

Initially	O
the	O
economy	O
of	O
Java	B-LOC	X
relied	O
heavily	O
on	O
rice	O
agriculture	O
.	O

Ancient	O
kingdoms	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
Tarumanagara	B-LOC
,	O
Mataram	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Majapahit	B-LOC
were	O
dependent	O
on	O
rice	O
yields	O
and	O
tax	O
.	O

Java	B-LOC	X
was	O
famous	O
for	O
rice	O
surpluses	O
and	O
rice	O
export	O
since	O
ancient	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
rice	O
agriculture	O
contributed	O
to	O
the	O
population	O
growth	O
of	O
the	O
island	O
.	O

Trade	O
with	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
Asia	B-LOC
such	O
as	O
ancient	O
India	B-LOC
and	O
China	B-LOC
flourished	O
as	O
early	O
as	O
the	O
4th	O
century	O
,	O
as	O
evidenced	O
by	O
Chinese	O
ceramics	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
island	O
dated	O
to	O
that	O
period	O
.	O

Java	B-LOC	X
also	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
global	O
trade	O
of	O
Maluku	B-LOC
spice	O
from	O
ancient	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Majapahit	B-LOC
era	O
,	O
until	O
well	O
into	O
the	O
Dutch	B-ORG
East	I-ORG
India	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
(	O
VOC	B-ORG
)	O
era	O
.

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Corymbia_citriodora

Corymbia	O	X
citriodora	O
is	O
a	O
tall	O
tree	O
,	O
growing	O
to	O
35	O
metres	O
(	O
115	O
ft	O
)	O
in	O
height	O
(	O
but	O
sometimes	O
taller	O
)	O
,	O
from	O
temperate	O
and	O
tropical	O
north	O
eastern	O
Australia	B-LOC
.	O


Plants	O
of	O
C	O
.	O
citriodora	O
are	O
naturalised	O
in	O
the	O
Darling	B-LOC
Range	I-LOC
near	O
Mundaring	B-LOC
,	O
Western	B-LOC
Australia	I-LOC
and	O
by	O
planting	O
to	O
suburban	O
New	B-LOC
South	I-LOC
Wales	I-LOC
,	O
South	B-LOC
Australia	I-LOC
and	O
Victoria	B-LOC
.	O

Kings	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
in	O
Perth	B-LOC
has	O
a	O
famous	O
,	O
beautiful	O
avenue	O
of	O
this	O
species	O
planted	O
many	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
spread	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
serious	O
weed	O
.	O

Corymbia	O	X
citriodora	O
is	O
an	O
important	O
forest	O
tree	O
,	O
in	O
demand	O
for	O
structural	O
timber	O
and	O
for	O
honey	O
production	O
.	O

It	O
also	O
is	O
popular	O
in	O
horticulture	O
both	O
within	O
Australia	B-LOC
and	O
overseas	O
.	O

The	O
name	O
Corymbia	O	X
citriodora	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
Latin	O
citriodorus	O
,	O
which	O
means	O
lemon-scented	O
.	O

Many	O
naturalists	O
and	O
conservationists	O
do	O
not	O
recognise	O
the	O
Corymbia	O	X
genus	O
and	O
still	O
categorise	O
its	O
species	O
within	O
Eucalyptus	O
.	O

Corymbia	O	X
is	O
a	O
genus	O
of	O
about	O
113	O
species	O
of	O
tree	O
that	O
were	O
classified	O
as	O
Eucalyptus	O
species	O
until	O
the	O
mid-1990s	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Precambrian

The	O	X
Precambrian	O	X
(	O
or	O
Pre-Cambrian	O	X
,	O
sometimes	O
abbreviated	O
pЄ	O
,	O
or	O
Cryptozoic	O
)	O
is	O
the	O
earliest	O
part	O
of	O
Earth	B-LOC
's	O
history	O
,	O
set	O
before	O
the	O
current	O
Phanerozoic	O
Eon	O
.	O

The	O	X
Precambrian	O	X
is	O
so	O
named	O
because	O
it	O
preceded	O
the	O
Cambrian	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
period	O
of	O
the	O
Phanerozoic	O
eon	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
named	O
after	O
Cambria	O
,	O
the	O
Latinised	O
name	O
for	O
Wales	B-LOC
,	O
where	O
rocks	O
from	O
this	O
age	O
were	O
first	O
studied	O
.	O

The	O	X
Precambrian	O	X
accounts	O
for	O
88	O
%	O
of	O
the	O
Earth	B-LOC
's	O
geologic	O
time	O
.

Relatively	O
little	O
is	O
known	O
about	O
the	O	X
Precambrian	O	X
,	O
despite	O
it	O
making	O
up	O
roughly	O
seven	O
-	O
eighths	O
of	O
the	O
Earth	B-LOC
's	O
history	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
known	O
has	O
largely	O
been	O
discovered	O
from	O
the	O
1960s	O
onwards	O
.	O

The	O	X
Precambrian	O	X
fossil	O
record	O
is	O
poorer	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
succeeding	O
Phanerozoic	O
,	O
and	O
fossils	O
from	O
the	O	X
Precambrian	O	X
(	O
e.g.	O
stromatolites	O
)	O
are	O
of	O
limited	O
biostratigraphic	O
use	O
.	O

This	O
is	O
because	O
many	O
Precambrian	O	X
rocks	O
have	O
been	O
heavily	O
metamorphosed	O
,	O
obscuring	O
their	O
origins	O
,	O
while	O
others	O
have	O
been	O
destroyed	O
by	O
erosion	O
,	O
or	O
remain	O
deeply	O
buried	O
beneath	O
Phanerozoic	O
strata	O
.

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Butylated_hydroxytoluene

Butylated	O
hydroxytoluene	O
(	O
BHT	O	X
)	O
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
dibutylhydroxytoluene	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
lipophilic	O
organic	O
compound	O
,	O
chemically	O
a	O
derivative	O
of	O
phenol	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
useful	O
for	O
its	O
antioxidant	O
properties	O
.	O

European	O
and	O
U.S.	B-LOC
regulations	O
allow	O
small	O
amounts	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
as	O
a	O
food	O
additive	O
.	O

In	O
addition	O
to	O
this	O
use	O
,	O
BHT	O	X
is	O
widely	O
used	O
to	O
prevent	O
oxidation	O
in	O
fluids	O
(	O
e.g.	O
fuel	O
,	O
oil	O
)	O
and	O
other	O
materials	O
where	O
free	O
radicals	O
must	O
be	O
controlled	O
.	O

The	O
US	B-ORG
Food	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Drug	I-ORG
Administration	I-ORG
classifies	O
BHT	O	X
as	O
generally	O
recognized	O
as	O
safe	O
(	O
GRAS	O
)	O
as	O
a	O
food	O
preservative	O
when	O
used	O
according	O
to	O
approved	O
uses	O
.	O

There	O
is	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
some	O
debate	O
surrounding	O
a	O
possible	O
link	O
between	O
BHT	O	X
and	O
cancer	O
risk	O
,	O
asthma	O
,	O
and	O
behavioral	O
issues	O
in	O
children	O
;	O
some	O
studies	O
show	O
a	O
potential	O
to	O
increase	O
risk	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
decrease	O
risk	O
.	O

Because	O
of	O
this	O
uncertainty	O
,	O
the	O
consumer	O
group	O
Center	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Public	I-ORG
Interest	I-ORG
recommend	O
to	O
avoid	O
BHT	O	X
and	O
puts	O
BHT	O	X
in	O
its	O
"	O
caution	O
"	O
column	O
.

The	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Cancer	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
determined	O
in	O
1979	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
noncarcinogenic	O
in	O
a	O
mouse	O
model	O
.	O

BHT	O	X
has	O
low	O
acute	O
toxicity	O
,	O
as	O
do	O
other	O
closely	O
related	O
phenol	O
antioxidants	O
.

For	O
example	O
,	O
the	O
LD50	O
of	O
2,6	O
-	O
di	O
-	O
tert	O
-	O
butylphenol	O
is	O
greater	O
than	O
9	O
g	O
/	O
kg	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magdalena_%C3%81lvarez

Magdalena	B-PER	X
Álvarez	I-PER	X
was	O
an	O
MP	O
in	O
the	O
Andalusian	O
parliament	O
for	O
the	O
province	O
of	O
Málaga	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
in	O
August	O
1994	O
she	O
was	O
named	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Economy	O
and	O
Revenue	O
for	O
the	O
Junta	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
Andalucía	I-ORG
,	O
becoming	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
cabinet	O
of	O
Manuel	B-PER
Chaves	I-PER
.	O

In	O
the	O
subsequent	O
elections	O
,	O
in	O
March	O
2000	O
,	O
Chaves	B-PER
kept	O
her	O
as	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Ministry	O
of	O
Economy	O
and	O
Revenue	O
for	O
the	O
sixth	O
Andaluz	O
Parliament	O
.	O

On	O
2	O
July	O
2013	O
Alvarez	B-PER	X
was	O
formally	O
charged	O
by	O
Judge	O
Alaya	B-PER
in	O
the	O
ERE	O
case	O
in	O
Andalusia	B-LOC
,	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
consistent	O
pattern	O
of	O
alleged	O
misappropriation	O
of	O
public	O
funds	O
between	O
2001	O
and	O
2010	O
under	O
the	O
leadership	O
of	O
the	O
PSOE	B-ORG
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HVAC_control_system

HVAC	O	X
(	O
Heating	O
,	O
Ventilation	O
and	O
Air	O
Conditioning	O
)	O
equipment	O
needs	O
a	O
control	O
system	O
to	O
regulate	O
the	O
operation	O
of	O
a	O
heating	O
and	O
/	O
or	O
air	O
conditioning	O
system	O
.	O

Usually	O
a	O
sensing	O
device	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
compare	O
the	O
actual	O
state	O
(	O
e.g.	O
temperature	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
target	O
state	O
.	O

Then	O
the	O
control	O
system	O
draws	O
a	O
conclusion	O
what	O
action	O
has	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
(	O
e.g.	O
start	O
the	O
blower	O
)	O
.	O

More	O
complex	O
HVAC	O	X
systems	O
can	O
interface	O
to	O
Building	O
Automation	O
System	O
(	O
BAS	O
)	O
to	O
allow	O
the	O
building	O
owners	O
to	O
have	O
more	O
control	O
over	O
the	O
heating	O
or	O
cooling	O
units	O
.	O

The	O
building	O
owner	O
can	O
monitor	O
the	O
system	O
and	O
respond	O
to	O
alarms	O
generated	O
by	O
the	O
system	O
from	O
local	O
or	O
remote	O
locations	O
.	O

The	O
system	O
can	O
be	O
scheduled	O
for	O
occupancy	O
or	O
the	O
configuration	O
can	O
be	O
changed	O
from	O
the	O
BAS	O
.	O

Sometimes	O
the	O
BAS	O
is	O
directly	O
controlling	O
the	O
HVAC	O	X
components	O
.	O

Depending	O
on	O
the	O
BAS	O
different	O
interfaces	O
can	O
be	O
used	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Parectopa_ononidis

Parectopa	O	X
ononidis	O	X
is	O
a	O
moth	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
Gracillariidae	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
known	O
from	O
all	O
of	O
Europe	B-LOC
,	O
except	O
Ireland	B-LOC
and	O
the	O
Balkan	B-LOC
Peninsula	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
wingspan	O
is	O
about	O
8	O
mm	O
.	O

Adults	O
are	O
on	O
wing	O
from	O
May	O
to	O
August	O
in	O
two	O
to	O
three	O
generations	O
per	O
year	O
.	O

The	O
larvae	O
feed	O
on	O
Ononis	O
repens	O
,	O
Ononis	O
spinosa	O
,	O
Trifolium	O
medium	O
,	O
Trifolium	O
montanum	O
,	O
Trifolium	O
ochroleucum	O
,	O
Trifolium	O
pratense	O
and	O
Trifolium	O
repens	O
.	O

The	O
mine	O
starts	O
as	O
a	O
small	O
,	O
lower-surface	O
epidermal	O
corridor	O
.	O

Only	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
moult	O
the	O
larva	O
starts	O
feeding	O
on	O
the	O
leaf	O
parenchyma	O
,	O
resulting	O
in	O
a	O
corridor	O
overlying	O
the	O
midrib	O
.	O

From	O
here	O
branches	O
enter	O
the	O
leaf	O
disk	O
,	O
gradually	O
widening	O
and	O
merging	O
,	O
leaving	O
almost	O
the	O
entire	O
mine	O
mined	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
.	O

Most	O
frass	O
is	O
ejected	O
.	O

The	O
larva	O
may	O
leave	O
the	O
mine	O
and	O
start	O
elsewhere	O
.	O

Pupation	O
takes	O
place	O
within	O
the	O
mine	O
.	O

Species	O
:	O
P	O	X
.	O	X
ononidis	O	X

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/78_Saab

78	B-ORG	X
Saab	I-ORG	X
formed	O
at	O
the	O
Australian	B-LOC
National	I-LOC
University	I-LOC
,	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
members	O
being	O
Nash	B-PER
,	O
Tregillgas	B-PER
,	O
Darren	B-PER
Smith	I-PER
and	O
Christovac	B-PER
Thompson	I-PER
.	O

For	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
attaining	O
live	O
performance	O
experience	O
,	O
they	O
entered	O
the	O
Australian	O
National	O
Campus	O
Band	O
Competition	O
in	O
1996	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
band	O
name	O
chosen	O
spontaneously	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
complete	O
the	O
entry	O
form	O
.	O

After	O
its	O
release	O
in	O
1997	O
,	O
78	B-ORG	X
Saab	I-ORG	X
prepared	O
for	O
a	O
run	O
of	O
35	O
dates	O
to	O
promote	O
the	O
EP	O
.	O

Before	O
the	O
tour	O
began	O
however	O
,	O
Darren	B-PER
Smith	I-PER
made	O
the	O
decision	O
not	O
to	O
continue	O
with	O
the	O
band	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ekwendeni

Ekwendeni	B-LOC	X
is	O
a	O
town	O
in	O
the	O
Northern	O
Region	O
of	O
Malawi	B-LOC
.	O

It	O
lies	O
about	O
20	O
kilometres	O
(	O
12	O
mi	O
)	O
from	O
Mzuzu	B-LOC
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mzimba	B-LOC
district	O
.	O

Ekwendeni	B-LOC	X
was	O
started	O
by	O
Scottish	O
missionaries	O
.	O

In	O
1889	O
Walter	B-PER
Angus	I-PER
Elmslie	I-PER
opened	O
a	O
mission	O
station	O
at	O
Ekwendeni	B-LOC	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Courtney_Love

A	O
figure	O
in	O
the	O
punk	O
and	O
grunge	O
scenes	O
of	O
the	O
1990s	O
,	O
Love	B-PER	X
's	O
career	O
has	O
spanned	O
four	O
decades	O
.	O

She	O
rose	O
to	O
prominence	O
as	O
the	O
lead	O
vocalist	O
of	O
the	O
alternative	O
rock	O
band	O
Hole	B-ORG
,	O
which	O
she	O
formed	O
in	O
1989	O
.	O

Love	B-PER	X
has	O
drawn	O
public	O
attention	O
for	O
her	O
uninhibited	O
live	O
performances	O
and	O
confrontational	O
lyrics	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
highly	O
publicized	O
personal	O
life	O
following	O
her	O
marriage	O
to	O
Nirvana	B-ORG
frontman	O
Kurt	B-PER
Cobain	I-PER
.	O

Love	B-PER	X
was	O
subject	O
of	O
a	O
second	O
landmark	O
libel	O
lawsuit	O
brought	O
against	O
her	O
in	O
January	O
2014	O
by	O
her	O
former	O
attorney	O
Rhonda	B-PER
Holmes	I-PER
,	O
who	O
accused	O
Love	B-PER	X
of	O
online	O
defamation	O
,	O
seeking	O
$8	O
million	O
in	O
damages	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
case	O
of	O
alleged	O
Twitter	B-ORG
-	O
based	O
libel	O
in	O
U.S.	B-LOC
history	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
to	O
trial	O
.

The	O
jury	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
Love	B-PER	X
's	O
favor	O
.	O

A	O
subsequent	O
defamation	O
lawsuit	O
filed	O
by	O
fashion	O
Simorangkir	B-PER
in	O
February	O
2014	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
resulted	O
in	O
Love	B-PER	X
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
further	O
$350	O
,	O
000	O
in	O
recompense	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tamer_Institute_for_Community_Education

The	O
Tamer	B-ORG	X
Institute	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Community	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
is	O
a	O
non-profit	O
non-governmental	O
educational	O
organization	O
working	O
in	O
Palestine	B-LOC
.	O

It	O
was	O
established	O
in	O
1989	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
Palestinian	O
needs	O
during	O
the	O
first	O
intifada	O
.	O

Tamer	B-ORG	X
works	O
primarily	O
with	O
and	O
for	O
children	O
and	O
young	O
people	O
,	O
providing	O
safe	O
,	O
friendly	O
learning	O
environments	O
and	O
materials	O
.	O

Tamer	B-ORG	X
runs	O
a	O
publishing	O
unit	O
,	O
publish	O
a	O
newsletter	O
,	O
hold	O
courses	O
for	O
librarians	O
,	O
arranges	O
workshops	O
,	O
donate	O
books	O
to	O
local	O
libraries	O
and	O
arranges	O
an	O
annual	O
reading	O
-	O
and	O
writing	O
campaign	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dragon_Dynasty

Dragon	B-ORG	X
Dynasty	I-ORG	X
is	O
a	O
joint	O
venture	O
started	O
by	O
Bleecker	B-ORG
Street	I-ORG
,	O
The	B-ORG
Weinstein	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
and	O
Genius	B-ORG
Products	I-ORG
.	O

On	O
19	O
June	O
2007	O
,	O
Dragon	B-ORG	O
Dynasty	I-ORG	O
released	O
the	O
film	O
My	O
Young	O
Auntie	O
.

The	O
film	O
was	O
originally	O
produced	O
in	O
Hong	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC
by	O
Shaw	B-ORG
Brothers	I-ORG
in	O
1981	O
and	O
was	O
accordingly	O
released	O
with	O
a	O
Cantonese	O
soundtrack	O
as	O
standard	O
.	O

However	O
,	O
Dragon	B-ORG	O
Dynasty	I-ORG	O
's	O
DVD	O
features	O
only	O
the	O
Mandarin	O
and	O
English	O
dubbed	O
soundtracks	O
.	O

Whilst	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
cast	O
spoke	O
Mandarin	O
during	O
filming	O
(	O
as	O
is	O
often	O
the	O
case	O
with	O
Hong	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC
film	O
productions	O
)	O
,	O
the	O
main	O
star	O
(	O
Kara	B-PER
Hui	I-PER
)	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
cast	O
members	O
spoke	O
Cantonese	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/STMicroelectronics

STMicroelectronics	B-ORG	X
is	O
a	O
French-Italian	O
multinational	O
electronics	O
and	O
semiconductor	O
manufacturer	O
headquartered	O
in	O
Geneva	B-LOC
,	O
Switzerland	B-LOC
.

It	O
is	O
commonly	O
called	O
ST	B-ORG	X
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
Europe	B-LOC
's	O
largest	O
semiconductor	O
chip	O
maker	O
based	O
on	O
revenue	O
.

In	O
2011	O
,	O
ST	B-ORG	X
announced	O
the	O
creation	O
of	O
a	O
joint	O
lab	O
with	O
Sant'Anna	B-ORG
School	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Advanced	I-ORG
Studies	I-ORG
.

The	O
lab	O
will	O
focus	O
on	O
research	O
and	O
innovation	O
in	O
bio-robotics	O
,	O
smart	O
systems	O
and	O
microelectronics	O
.

Past	O
collaborations	O
with	O
Sant'Anna	B-ORG
School	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Advanced	I-ORG
Studies	-ORG
included	O
DustBot	O
,	O
a	O
platform	O
that	O
integrated	O
self-navigating	O
"	O
service	O
robots	O
"	O
for	O
waste	O
collection	O
.

ST	B-ORG
Ericsson	I-ORG
was	O
a	O
multinational	O
manufacturer	O
of	O
wireless	O
products	O
and	O
semiconductors	O
,	O
supplying	O
to	O
mobile	O
device	O
manufacturers	O
.

ST-Ericsson	B-ORG
was	O
a	O
50/50	O
joint	O
venture	O
of	O
Ericsson	B-ORG
and	O
STMicroelectronics	B-ORG
established	O
on	O
February	O
3	O
,	O
2009	O
,	O
and	O
dissolved	O
on	O
August	O
2	O
,	O
2013	O
.

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HMS_Pakenham

Three	O
ships	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	B-ORG
Navy	I-ORG
have	O
been	O
named	O
HMS	O	X
Pakenham	O	X
,	O
after	O
Admiral	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-PER
Pakenham	I-PER
:	O

The	O
first	O
HMS	O	X
Pakenham	O	X
(	O
1797	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
1-gun	O
gunvessel	O
purchased	O
in	O
1797	O
.	O

She	O
was	O
in	O
service	O
in	O
1800	O
and	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
sold	O
in	O
1802	O
.	O

The	O
second	O
HMS	O	X
Pakenham	O	X
was	O
an	O
O-class	O
destroyer	O
.	O

She	O
was	O
renamed	O
HMS	O
Onslow	O
(	O
G17	O
)	O
shortly	O
after	O
being	O
launched	O
in	O
1941	O
.	O

The	O
third	O
HMS	O	X
Pakenham	O	X
(	O
G06	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
P-class	O
destroyer	O
built	O
as	O
HMS	O
Onslow	O
but	O
renamed	O
shortly	O
after	O
being	O
launched	O
in	O
1941	O
.	O

She	O
was	O
disabled	O
in	O
a	O
night	O
encounter	O
off	O
Marsala	B-LOC
by	O
Italian	O
torpedo	O
boats	O
in	O
1943	O
and	O
was	O
scuttled	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Order_of_New_Zealand

The	O	X
Order	O	X
of	O	X
New	O	X
Zealand	O	X
is	O
the	O
highest	O
honour	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC
's	O
royal	O
honours	O
system	O
,	O
created	O
"	O
to	O
recognise	O
outstanding	O
service	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
people	O
of	O
New	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC
in	O
a	O
civil	O
or	O
military	O
capacity	O
"	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
instituted	O
by	O
royal	O
warrant	O
of	O
6	O
February	O
1987	O
.	O

The	O
order	O
is	O
modelled	O
on	O
the	O
British	O
Order	O
of	O
Merit	O
and	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Companions	O
of	O
Honour	O
.	O

Honorary	O
membership	O
is	O
for	O
citizens	O
of	O
nations	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Sovereign	O
is	O
not	O
head	O
of	O
state	O
.	O

Members	O
are	O
entitled	O
to	O
the	O
post-nominal	O
letters	O
"	O
ONZ	O	X
"	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sugar_Gibiliru

Sugar	B-PER	X
Gibiliru	I-PER	X
was	O
unbeaten	O
in	O
his	O
next	O
four	O
fights	O
,	O
setting	O
up	O
a	O
challenge	O
for	O
Robert	B-PER
Dickie	I-PER
's	O
British	O
title	O
in	O
April	O
1991	O
.	O

Gibiliru	B-PER	X
stopped	O
Dickie	B-PER
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
round	O
to	O
become	O
British	O
champion	O
.	O

Sugar	B-PER	X
lost	O
the	O
title	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
defence	O
,	O
losing	O
on	O
points	O
to	O
John	B-PER
Doherty	I-PER
in	O
September	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toni_Ti%C5%A1lar

Tislar	B-PER	X
won	O
the	O
Yugoslav	O
Ice	O
Hockey	O
League	O
title	O
with	O
HK	B-ORG
Acroni	I-ORG
Jesenice	I-ORG
in	O
1988	O
and	O
1989	O
.	O

He	O
played	O
with	O
HDD	B-ORG
Olimpija	I-ORG
Ljubljana	I-ORG
from	O
1991	O
–	O
1995	O
,	O
HK	B-ORG
MK	I-ORG
Bled	I-ORG
from	O
1995	O
–	O
1997	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
2002	O
–	O
03	O
.	O

Tislar	B-PER	X
participated	O
in	O
10	O
IIHF	O
World	O
Championships	O
with	O
Yugoslavia	B-LOC
and	O
Slovenia	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sadaaki_Akamatsu

Sadaaki	B-PER	X
Akamatsu	I-PER	X
was	O
credited	O
with	O
shooting	O
down	O
11	O
enemy	O
aircraft	O
over	O
China	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Sino	O
-	O
Japanese	O
War	O
,	O
including	O
four	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
engagement	O
near	O
Nanchang	B-LOC
on	O
25	O
February	O
1938	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
opening	O
months	O
of	O
the	O
Pacific	O
War	O
,	O
Akamatsu	B-PER	X
served	O
in	O
the	O
Philippines	B-LOC
and	O
Dutch	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
Indies	I-LOC
campaigns	O
.	O

From	O
January	O
1944	O
until	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
war	O
,	O
Akamatsu	B-PER	X
flew	O
out	O
of	O
Atsugi	B-LOC
Air	I-LOC
Base	I-LOC
,	O
defending	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
from	O
Allied	O
air	O
attacks	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Ruins_of_Adventure

The	O
Ruins	O
of	O
Adventure	O
is	O
the	O
49th	O
album	O
by	O
avant-folk	O
Jandek	B-PER	X
,	O
the	O
45th	O
'	O
studio	O
'	O
album	O
released	O
by	O
Corwood	B-ORG
Industries	I-ORG
around	O
December	O
2006	O
.	O

The	O
photograph	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
album	O
's	O
front	O
cover	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
one	O
used	O
for	O
Jandek	B-PER	X
's	O
previous	O
release	O
What	O
Else	O
Does	O
The	O
Time	O
Mean	O
?	O
,	O
only	O
instead	O
cropped	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
.	O

After	O
a	O
few	O
consecutive	O
live	O
releases	O
,	O
this	O
album	O
finds	O
the	O
artist	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
sounding	O
studio	O
playing	O
solo	O
fretless	O
bass	O
and	O
vocals	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Farrukhan_the_Great

Farrukhan	B-PER	X
the	I-PER	X
Great	B-PER	X
was	O
the	O
independent	O
ruler	O
(	O
ispahbadh	O
)	O
of	O
Tabaristan	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
early	O
8th	O
century	O
,	O
until	O
his	O
death	O
in	O
728	O
.	O

Farrukhan	B-PER	X
is	O
the	O
first	O
actually	O
attested	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Dabuyid	O
dynasty	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
traditionally	O
held	O
to	O
have	O
ruled	O
Tabaristan	B-LOC
since	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Muslim	O
conquest	O
of	O
Persia	B-LOC
.	O

Farrukhan	B-PER	X
maintained	O
the	O
independence	O
against	O
the	O
attacks	O
of	O
the	O
Umayyad	B-ORG
Caliphate	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
was	O
succeeded	O
by	O
Dadhburzmihr	B-PER
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nadir_Belhadj

Nadir	B-PER	X
Belhadj	I-PER	X
played	O
a	O
vital	O
role	O
for	O
Qatari	O
club	O
Al	B-ORG
Sadd	I-ORG
in	O
the	O
2011	O
Asian	O
Champions	O
League	O
final	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
South	O
Korean	O
side	O
Jeonbuk	B-ORG
Hyundai	I-ORG
Motors	I-ORG
4	O
–	O
2	O
in	O
a	O
penalty	O
shoot	O
-	O
out	O
.	O

In	O
January	O
2007	O
Belhadj	B-PER	X
was	O
bought	O
by	O
French	O
champions	O
Olympique	B-ORG
Lyonnais	I-LOC
for	O
€	O
3.24	O
million	O
and	O
signed	O
a	O
lucrative	O
four	O
and	O
a	O
half-year	O
deal	O
.	O

On	O
1	O
September	O
2008	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
announced	O
that	O
Portsmouth	B-ORG
had	O
signed	O
Belhadj	B-PER	X
on	O
a	O
season	O
-	O
long	O
loan	O
with	O
an	O
option	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
deal	O
permanent	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tennys_Sandgren

Tennys	B-PER	X
Sandgren	I-PER	X
began	O
his	O
season	O
with	O
a	O
first	O
round	O
loss	O
to	O
eventual	O
champion	O
Gilles	B-PER
Simon	I-PER
in	O
Pune	O
.	O

Following	O
a	O
first	O
round	O
loss	O
against	O
Frances	B-PER
Tiafoe	I-PER
at	O
the	O
Estoril	O
Open	O
,	O
Sandgren	B-PER	X
suffered	O
his	O
fourth	O
consecutive	O
first	O
round	O
loss	O
,	O
losing	O
in	O
straight	O
sets	O
to	O
Denis	B-PER
Shapovalov	I-PER
at	O
the	O
Madrid	O
Open	O
.	O

After	O
having	O
reached	O
the	O
quarterfinals	O
at	O
the	O
Geneva	O
Open	O
,	O
Sandgren	B-PER	X
was	O
knocked	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
round	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Open	O
by	O
world	O
No	O
.	O
177	O
and	O
qualifier	O
Hubert	B-PER
Hurkacz	I-PER
.	O

Sandgren	B-PER	X
also	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
round	O
of	O
the	O
doubles	O
tournament	O
in	O
straight	O
sets	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1975_Ryder_Cup

The	O
21st	O
Ryder	O
Cup	O
Matches	O
were	O
held	O
September	O
19	O
–	O
21	O
at	O
Laurel	B-ORG	X
Valley	I-ORG	X
Golf	I-ORG	X
Club	I-ORG	X
in	O
Ligonier	B-LOC
,	O
Pennsylvania	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
Ryder	O
Cup	O
is	O
a	O
match	O
play	O
event	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
match	O
worth	O
one	O
point	O
.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
team	O
won	O
the	O
competition	O
by	O
a	O
score	O
of	O
21	O
to	O
11	O
points	O
.	O

The	O
next	O
time	O
the	O
competition	O
was	O
held	O
in	O
the	O
U.S.	B-LOC
in	O
1979	O
,	O
the	O
visiting	O
team	O
included	O
players	O
from	O
continental	O
Europe	B-LOC
.	O

Laurel	B-ORG	X
Valley	I-ORG	X
was	O
co-founded	O
by	O
U.S.	B-LOC
captain	O
Arnold	B-PER
Palmer	I-PER
and	O
had	O
hosted	O
the	O
PGA	O
Championship	O
a	O
decade	O
earlier	O
,	O
in	O
1965	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Asleep_at_the_Wheel

Asleep	B-ORG	X
at	I-ORG	X
the	I-ORG	X
Wheel	I-ORG	X
is	O
an	O
American	O
country	O
music	O
group	O
that	O
was	O
formed	O
in	O
Paw	B-LOC
Paw	I-LOC
,	O
West	B-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
and	O
is	O
based	O
in	O
Austin	B-LOC
,	O
Texas	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
band	O
has	O
won	O
nine	O
Grammy	O
Awards	O
since	O
their	O
1970	O
inception	O
,	O
released	O
over	O
twenty	O
albums	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
charted	O
more	O
than	O
21	O
singles	O
on	O
the	O
Billboard	O
country	O
charts	O
.	O

Asleep	B-ORG	X
at	I-ORG	X
the	I-ORG	X
Wheel	I-ORG	X
gathered	O
a	O
large	O
amount	O
of	O
debt	O
that	O
required	O
them	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
commercials	O
and	O
movie	O
soundtracks	O
.	O

Asleeps	B-ORG	X
produced	O
the	O
soundtrack	O
for	O
the	O
film	O
Liar	O
's	O
Moon	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jes%C3%BAs_Enrique_Rej%C3%B3n_Aguilar

In	O
1997	O
,	O
Jesús	B-PER	X
Enrique	I-PER	X
Rejón	I-PER	X
Aguilar	I-PER	X
was	O
assigned	O
to	O
the	O
Mexico	B-LOC
’s	O
Federal	B-ORG
Attorney	I-ORG
General	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Office	I-ORG
(	O
PGR	B-ORG
)	O
in	O
the	O
cities	O
of	O
Reynosa	B-LOC
and	O
Miguel	B-LOC
Alemán	I-LOC
in	O
Tamaulipas	B-LOC
.	O

Rejón	B-PER	X
Aguilar	I-PER	X
is	O
responsible	O
for	O
multi	O
-	O
ton	O
shipments	O
of	O
marijuana	O
and	O
multi	O
-	O
kilogram	O
shipments	O
of	O
cocaine	O
from	O
Mexico	B-LOC
to	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
.	O

In	O
2004	O
,	O
Rejón	B-PER	X
Aguilar	I-PER	X
coordinated	O
a	O
failed	O
raid	O
on	O
the	O
maximum	O
security	O
prison	O
'	O
El	B-LOC
Altiplano	I-LOC
'	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/118th_J%C3%A4ger_Division_(Wehrmacht)

The	O
118th	B-ORG	X
Jäger	I-ORG	X
Division	I-ORG	X
was	O
a	O
light	O
infantry	O
division	O
of	O
the	O
German	B-ORG
Army	I-ORG
in	O
World	O
War	O
II	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
formed	O
in	O
April	O
1943	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
redesignation	O
of	O
the	O
718th	B-ORG
Infantry	I-ORG
Division	I-ORG
which	O
had	O
itself	O
been	O
formed	O
in	O
April	O
1941	O
.	O

The	O
118th	B-ORG	X
Jäger	I-ORG	X
was	O
transferred	O
to	O
Yugoslavia	B-LOC
in	O
May	O
1941	O
,	O
to	O
conduct	O
anti	O
partisan	O
and	O
Internal	O
security	O
operations	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Douglas_Emlong

Douglas	B-PER	X
Ralph	I-PER	X
Emlong	I-PER	X
was	O
an	O
amateur	O
fossil	O
collector	O
from	O
the	O
Oregon	B-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
northwestern	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
.	O

Emlong	B-PER	X
's	O
collections	O
contributed	O
to	O
the	O
discovery	O
and	O
description	O
of	O
numerous	O
extinct	O
marine	O
mammal	O
species	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
which	O
are	O
ancestral	O
to	O
extant	O
groups	O
.	O

Described	O
as	O
an	O
'	O
indefatigable	O
'	O
fossil	O
collector	O
with	O
'	O
Promethian	O
prowess	O
in	O
discovery	O
of	O
unprecedented	O
vertebrate	O
fossils	O
'	O
,	O
he	O
contributed	O
substantially	O
to	O
the	O
field	O
from	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
fourteen	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tokaido_(company)

In	O
1958	O
,	O
Sugiura	B-PER	X
established	O
the	O
Tokaido	B-ORG
company	O
.	O

Its	O
name	O
means	O
Eastern	O
Sea	O
Shop	O
in	O
Japanese	O
,	O
and	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sugiura	B-PER	X
's	O
home	O
region	O
on	O
the	O
east	O
coast	O
of	O
Honshū	B-LOC
island	O
.	O

Sugiura	B-PER	X
began	O
supplying	O
sample	O
uniforms	O
to	O
instructors	O
of	O
the	O
newly	O
formed	O
Japan	B-ORG
Karate	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
JKA	B-ORG
)	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
their	O
feedback	O
to	O
improve	O
the	O
designs	O
and	O
manufacturing	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Conyers,_Georgia

Conyers	B-LOC	O	X
is	O
the	O
only	O
city	O
in	O
Rockdale	B-LOC	X
County	I-LOC	X
,	O
Georgia	B-LOC	X
,	O
United	B-LOC	X
States	I-LOC	X
.	O

The	O
city	O
is	O
twenty	O
-	O
four	O
miles	O
(	O
38.6	O
km	O
)	O
east	O
of	O
Atlanta	B-LOC
.	O

Conyers	B-LOC	X
was	O
also	O
home	O
to	O
"	O
sidewalk	O
churches	O
"	O
.	O

At	O
its	O
peak	O
,	O
Milstead	B-LOC
and	O
Conyers	B-LOC	X
had	O
a	O
private	O
railroad	O
which	O
delivered	O
products	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
cotton	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
mill	O
to	O
Conyers	B-LOC	X
for	O
shipping	O
to	O
the	O
textile	O
mills	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Idris_Elba

Idrissa	B-PER	X
Akuna	I-PER	X
Elba	I-PER	X
OBE	O
(	O
/	O
ˈ	O
ɪdrɪs	O
ˈ	O
ɛlbə	O
/	O
;	O
born	O
6	O
September	O
1972	O
)	O
is	O
an	O
English	O
actor	O
,	O
producer	O
, 	O
musician	O
and	O
DJ	O
,	O
known	O
for	O
playing	O
drug	O
trafficker	O
Stringer	B-PER
Bell	I-PER
on	O
the	O
HBO	B-ORG
series	O
The	O
Wire	O
,	O
DCI	O
John	B-PER
Luther	I-PER
on	O
the	O
BBC	O
One	O
series	O
Luther	B-PER
and	O
Nelson	B-PER
Mandela	I-PER
in	O
the	O
biographical	O
film	O
Mandela	B-PER
:	O
Long	O
Walk	O
to	O
Freedom	O
(	O
2013	O
)	O
.	O

He	O
has	O
been	O
nominated	O
four	O
times	O
for	O
a	O
Golden	O
Globe	O
Award	O
for	O
Best	O
Actor	O
–	O
Miniseries	O
or	O
Television	O
Film	O
,	O
winning	O
one	O
and	O
was	O
nominated	O
five	O
times	O
for	O
a	O
Primetime	O
Emmy	O
Award	O
.	O

Elba	B-PER	X
appeared	O
in	O
Ridley	B-PER
Scott	I-PER
's	O
American	O
Gangster	O
(	O
2007	O
)	O
and	O
Prometheus	O
(	O
2012	O
)	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Napoleon,_Ohio

Napoleon	B-LOC
's	O
economy 	O
is 	O
based 	O
on 	O
the 	O
manufacturing 	O
of 	O
a 	O
variety 	O
of 	O
goods	O
. 	O

A 	O
major 	O
employer 	O
is	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
largest 	O
Campbell	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Soup	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
plant	O
,	O
located	O
on	O
the	O
southeastern	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
also	O
Tenneco	B-ORG
owns	O
one	O
their	O
largest	O
Elastomer	O
Plants	O
there	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gorki_(band)

Gorki	B-ORG	X
was	O
a	O
Belgian	O
rock	O
group	O
,	O
in	O
its	O
most	O
recent	O
line-up	O
consisting	O
of	O
Luc	B-PER
De	I-PER
Vos	I-PER
(	O
lead	O
singer	O
and	O
guitarist	O
)	O
,	O
Luc	B-PER
Heyvaerts	I-PER
(	O
keyboard	O
and	O
clarinet	O
)	O
,	O
Erik	B-PER
Van	I-PER
Biesen	I-PER
(	O
bass	O
guitar	O
)	O
,	O
Thomas	B-PER
Vanelslander	I-PER
(	O
guitarist	O
)	O
and	O
Bert	B-PER
Huysentruyt	I-PER
(	O
drums	O
)	O
.	O

Three	O
songs	O
by	O
Gorki	B-ORG	X
were	O
number	O
one	O
hits	O
in	O
the	O
Studio	B-ORG
Brussel	I-ORG
alternative	O
hitlist	O
De	O
Afrekening	O
in	O
Belgium	B-LOC
:	O
'	O
Lieve	O
kleine	O
piranha	O
'	O
(	O
Gorky	B-ORG	X
,	O
1992	O
)	O
,	O
Schaduw	O
in	O
de	O
schemering	O
(	O
from	O
the	O
CD	O
'	O
Plan	O
B	O
'	O
)	O
and 	O
'	O
Joerie	O
'	O
in	O
2006	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Rice_School

Students	O
living	O
near	O
Rice	B-ORG	X
are	O
not	O
zoned	O
to	O
Rice	B-ORG	X
,	O
as	O
Rice	B-ORG	X
is	O
an	O
all-magnet	O
school	O
.	O

Individuals	O
living	O
near	O
Rice	B-ORG	X
are	O
zoned	O
to	O
either	O
Twain	B-ORG
or	O
Roberts	B-ORG
elementary	O
schools	O
and	O
Pershing	B-ORG
Middle	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sennett,_New_York

The	O
east	O
town	O
line	O
is	O
the	O
border	O
of	O
Onondaga	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
.	O

Sennett	B-LOC	X
is	O
in	O
the	O
Finger	B-LOC
Lakes	I-LOC
region	O
,	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
north	O
end	O
of	O
Owasco	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
and	O
Skaneateles	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kickers_Offenbach

However	O
,	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
1971	O
season	O
would	O
find	O
Kickers	B-ORG	X
Offenbach	I-ORG	X
at	O
the	O
centre	O
of	O
the	O
Bundesliga	O
scandal	O
.	O

The	O
club	O
president	O
,	O
Horst-Gregorio	B-PER
Canellas	I-PER
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
German	B-ORG
Football	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
Deutsche	B-ORG
Fussball	I-ORG
Bund	I-ORG
or	O
German	B-ORG
Football	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
)	O
after	O
being	O
approached	O
by	O
a	O
player	O
from	O
another	O
team	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
cash	O
bonus	O
for	O
that	O
club	O
's	O
effort	O
in	O
beating	O
one	O
of	O
Offenbach	B-ORG	X
's	O
rivals	O
in	O
the	O
fight	O
against	O
relegation	O
.	O

Receiving	O
no	O
help	O
from	O
league	O
officials	O
,	O
Canellas	B-PER
began	O
gathering	O
evidence	O
of	O
how	O
widespread	O
the	O
payoffs	O
were	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
end	O
more	O
than	O
fifty	O
players	O
from	O
seven	O
clubs	O
,	O
two	O
coaches	O
,	O
and	O
siX
game	O
officials	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
trying	O
to	O
influence	O
the	O
outcome	O
of	O
games	O
through	O
bribes	O
,	O
but	O
Canellas	B-PER
was	O
unable	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
club	O
from	O
relegation	O
.	O

The	O
club	O
central	O
to	O
the	O
scandal	O
–	O
Arminia	B-ORG
Bielefeld	I-ORG
–	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
punished	O
until	O
the	O
following	O
season	O
,	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
save	O
Offenbach	B-ORG	X
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Freddie_Mercury

After	O
completing	O
the	O
penultimate	O
verse	O
,	O
Mercury	B-PER	X
had	O
told	O
the	O
band	O
he	O
"	O
was	O
n't	O
feeling	O
that	O
great	O
"	O
and	O
stated	O
,	O
"	O
I	O
will	O
finish	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
next	O
time	O
”	O
.	O

However	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
it	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
studio	O
,	O
so	O
May	B-PER
later	O
recorded	O
the	O
final	O
verse	O
of	O
the	O
song	O
.	O

Tributes	O

A 	O
statue	O
in	O
Montreux	B-LOC
,	O
Switzerland	B-LOC
,	O
by	O
sculptor	O
Irena	B-PER
Sedlecká	I-PER
,	O
was	O
erected	O
as	O
a	O
tribute	O
to	O
Mercury	B-PER	X
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lemon_(developer)

Lemon	B-ORG	X
was	O
a	O
video	O
game	O
developer	O
founded	O
in	O
1994	O
by	O
Søren	B-PER
Hannibal	I-PER
and	O
Jacob	B-PER
Andersen	I-PER
,	O
who	O
had	O
previously	O
been	O
members	O
of	O
a	O
demoscene	O
group	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
.	O

Lemon	B-ORG	X
created	O
the	O
voxel-based	O
3D	O
shooter	O
Amok	O
,	O
for	O
Sega	O
Saturn	O
and	O
PC	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birch_Communications

Birch	B-ORG	X
had	O
1,400	O
employees	O
in	O
2014	O
,	O
with	O
around	O
450	O
people	O
working	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
Atlanta	B-LOC
Operations	I-LOC
Center	I-LOC
as	O
of	O
2016	O
.	O

Community	O
involvement	O

Birch	B-ORG	X
has	O
been	O
involved	O
in	O
various	O
philanthropic	O
efforts	O
and	O
community	O
projects	O
,	O
including	O
donating	O
toys	O
and	O
funds	O
to	O
the	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
Kids	B-ORG
Yule	I-ORG
Love	I-ORG
in	O
2011	O
,	O
co-sponsoring	O
the	O
International	O
Cherry	O
Blossom	O
Festival	O
in	O
2013	O
,	O
and	O
donating	O
funds	O
to	O
Atlanta	B-LOC
's	O
Woodruff	B-ORG
Arts	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
in	O
2014	O
.	O

Birch	B-ORG	X
invested	O
in	O
Macon	B-ORG
Charter	I-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
in	O
August	O
2015	O
,	O
donating	O
funds	O
,	O
computer	O
equipment	O
,	O
and	O
furniture	O
to	O
the	O
Georgia	B-LOC
charter	O
school	O
and	O
serving	O
as	O
a	O
technology	O
constultant	O
during	O
construction.	O


In	O
February	O
2016	O
,	O
Birch	B-ORG	X
donated	O
PCs	O
and	O
laptops	O
to	O
the	O
Metro	B-ORG
Atlanta	I-ORG
Task	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Homeless	I-ORG
to	O
be	O
used	O
for	O
job-training	O
at	O
the	O
Peachtree-Pine	B-ORG
shelter.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Milton_College

Milton	B-ORG	X
College	I-ORG
had	O
,	O
in	O
fact	O
,	O
been	O
struggling	O
financially	O
since	O
the	O
Great	O
Depression	O
,	O
50	O
years	O
earlier	O
.	O

Without	O
accreditation	O
,	O
the	O
college	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
seen	O
any	O
federal	O
loans	O
or	O
grants	O
,	O
adding	O
to	O
an	O
already	O
difficult	O
situation	O
of	O
decreasing	O
student	O
enrollment	O
.	O

Furthermore	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
longer	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
compete	O
with	O
schools	O
in	O
the	O
Wisconsin	B-LOC
State	I-LOC
University	O
System	O
.	O

Some	O
135	O
students	O
had	O
been	O
planning	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
campus	O
when	O
the	O
school	O
closed	O
,	O
many	O
with	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
credits	O
left	O
until	O
completion	O
of	O
their	O
studies	O
.	O

Officials	O
negotiated	O
with	O
other	O
campuses	O
to	O
accept	O
Milton	B-ORG	X
students	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Obsidian_Entertainment

Their	O
idea	O
was	O
rejected	O
,	O
and	O
Jeffrey	B-PER
instead	O
asked	O
Obsidian	B-ORG	X
to	O
create	O
a	O
follow-up	O
to	O
the	O
BioWare	B-ORG
-	O
developed	O
Star	O
Wars	O
:	O
Knights	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Republic	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
team	O
at	O
Obsidian	B-ORG	X
was	O
familiar	O
with	O
the	O
technology	O
that	O
the	O
original	O
game	O
used	O
.	O

The	O
partnership	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
companies	O
finalized	O
in	O
late	O
2003	O
,	O
and	O
development	O
of	O
the	O
game	O
,	O
which	O
became	O
Star	O
Wars	O
Knights	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Republic	O
II	O
:	O
The	O
Sith	O
Lords	O
,	O
began	O
in	O
October	O
2003	O
.	O

Obsidian	B-ORG	X
was	O
given	O
15	O
months	O
to	O
develop	O
The	O
Sith	O
Lords	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brooks_England

In	O
a	O
2014	O
interview	O
with	O
Feel	B-ORG
Desain	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
Brooks	B-ORG	X
spokesperson	O
stated	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
family	O
legend	O
,	O
the	O
company	O
began	O
when	O
founder	O
John	B-PER 	O
Boultbee	I-PER 	O
Brooks	I-PER
,	O
a	O
horse	O
saddle	O
manufacturer	O
,	O
tried	O
to	O
use	O
a	O
bicycle	O
after	O
his	O
horse	O
died	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
wooden	O
seat	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
.	O

As	O
a	O
result	O
,	O
he	O
vowed	O
to	O
set	O
about	O
solving	O
this	O
problem	O
and	O
Brooks	B-ORG	X
was	O
born	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Downton,_Wiltshire

Nunton	B-LOC
(	O
with	O
Bodenham	B-LOC
)	O
and	O
Standlynch	B-LOC
became	O
civil	O
parishes	O
in 	O
the	O
19th	O
century	O
,	O
then	O
as	O
the	O
population	O
grew	O
and	O
churches	O
were	O
built	O
,	O
Downton	B-LOC	X
was	O
reduced	O
in	O
size	O
.	O

In	O
1896	O
its	O
eastern	O
part	O
became	O
Redlynch	B-LOC
civil	O
parish	O
,	O
in	O
1897	O
Charlton	B-LOC
and	O
Witherington	B-LOC
were	O
united	O
with	O
Standlynch	B-LOC
to	O
form	O
the	O
civil	O
parish	O
of	O
Standlynch	B-LOC
with	O
Charlton	B-LOC
All	I-LOC
Saints	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
in	O
1923	O
Morgan	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Vale	I-LOC
and	O
Woodfalls	I-LOC
were	O
taken	O
to	O
form	O
a	O
new	O
civil	O
parish	O
.	O

Finally	O
,	O
in	O
1934	O
Standlynch	B-LOC
and	O
Charlton	B-LOC
were	O
reunited	O
with	O
Downton	B-LOC	X,	O
and	O
Morgan	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Vale	I-LOC
and	O
Woodfalls	B-LOC
were	O
added	O
to	O
Redlynch	B-LOC
.	O

For	O
about	O
a	O
decade	O
from	O
around	O
1961	O
,	O
Downton	B-LOC	X
had	O
an	O
important	O
part	O
to	O
play	O
in	O
British	O
motorsport	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Decima_gallery

At	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
artist	O
Derrick	B-PER
Welsh	I-PER
was	O
represented	O
by	O
and	O
closely	O
affiliated	O
to	O
Decima	B-ORG	X
.	O

In	O
April	O
1999	O
,	O
Decima	B-ORG	X
attempted	O
to	O
cause	O
another	O
splash	O
with	O
a	O
show	O
entitled	O
"	O
Was	O
Jesus	B-PER
a	O
Homosexual	O
?	O
"	O
which	O
was	O
organised	O
in	O
conjunction	O
with	O
political	O
philosopher	O
Richard	B-PER
Morley	I-PER
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Getty_Images

Beginning	O
in	O
2008	O
, 	O
Getty	B-ORG	X
Images	I-ORG	X
has	O
created	O
controversy	O
for	O
its	O
methods	O
of	O
pursuing	O
copyright	O
enforcement	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
its	O
photographers	O
.	O

Rather	O
than	O
pursue	O
a	O
policy	O
of	O
sending	O
"	O
cease	O
and	O
desist	O
"	O
notices	O
,	O
Getty	B-ORG	X
typically	O
mails	O
a	O
demand	O
letter	O
that	O
claims	O
substantial	O
monetary	O
damages	O
from	O
owners	O
of	O
websites	O
it	O
believes	O
infringed	O
on	O
their	O
photographers	O
'	O
copyrights	O
.	O

Getty	B-ORG	X
commonly	O
tries	O
to	O
intimidate	O
website	O
owners	O
by	O
sending	O
collection	O
agents	O
,	O
even	O
though	O
a	O
demand	O
letter	O
does	O
not	O
create	O
a	O
debt	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hess_Educational_Organization

HESS	B-ORG	X
International	I-ORG	X
Educational	I-ORG	X
Group	I-ORG	X 	O
(	O
Traditional	O
Chinese	O
:	O
何嘉仁國際文教團隊	B-ORG	X
;	O
Pinyin	O
:	O
Héjiārén	B-ORG	X
Wénjiào	I-ORG	X
Jīgòu	I-ORG	X
)	O
is	O
the	O
single	O
largest	O
private	O
provider	O
of	O
English	O
education	O
in	O
Taiwan	B-LOC
.	O

Hess	B-ORG	X
has	O
an	O
estimated	O
60,000	O
students	O
enrolled	O
.	O

Founded	O
in	O
1983	O
by	O
Joseph	B-PER
Chu	I-PER
and	O
Karen	B-PER
Hess	I-PER
,	O
it	O
has	O
become	O
a	O
large	O
business	O
,	O
with	O
schools	O
across	O
the	O
island	O
.	O

Hess	B-ORG	X
also	O
provides	O
books	O
and	O
resources	O
to	O
other	O
English	O
schools	O
across	O
Asia	B-LOC
to	O
teach	O
English	O
as	O
a	O
foreign	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
chain	O
of	O
bookstores	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
founded	O
in	O
1990	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jewel_(singer)

Jewel	B-PER	X
recently	O
founded	O
Jewel	B-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
platform	O
for	O
all	O
of	O
her	O
passions	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
music	O
,	O
tv	O
,	O
film	O
and	O
entrepreneurial	O
endeavors	O
.	O

Jewel	B-PER	X
is	O
creating	O
human	O
development	O
,	O
education	O
and	O
mindfulness	O
tools	O
for	O
individuals	O
by	O
collaborating	O
with	O
school	O
districts	O
,	O
corporations	O
and	O
consumers	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
helping	O
more	O
people	O
to	O
become	O
WHOLE	O
HUMANS	O
.	O

To	O
this	O
end	O
she	O
is	O
partnering	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
worlds	O
most	O
innovative	O
companies	O
(	O
Zappos	B-ORG
)	O
and	O
entrepreneurs	O
(	O
Tony	B-PER
Hsieh	I-PER
)	O
to	O
help	O
deliver	O
happiness	O
into	O
people	O
's	O
every	O
day	O
lives	O
,	O
at	O
work	O
and	O
at	O
home	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kennedy,_Wisconsin

Spur	O
lines	O
were	O
built	O
from	O
Kennedy	B-LOC	X
to	O
seven	O
logging	O
camps	O
to	O
the	O
north	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Ashland	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
border	O
.	O

In	O
1908	O
,	O
Willard	B-PER
Walther	I-PER
developed	O
the	O
plat	O
for	O
the	O
new	O
community	O
.	O

The	O
village	O
grew	O
as	O
the	O
logging	O
operations	O
drew	O
more	O
workers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cut-over	O
land	O
was	O
settled	O
.	O

A	O
log	O
schoolhouse	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
building	O
built	O
,	O
located	O
on	O
the	O
west	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
settlement	O
.	O

Taverns	O
,	O
a	O
boarding	O
house	O
,	O
general	O
store	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
train	O
station	O
also	O
soon	O
appeared	O
.	O

A	O
frame	O
schoolhouse	O
and	O
post	O
Office	O
were	O
built	O
in	O
1911	O
.	O

In	O
time	O
,	O
Kennedy	B-LOC	X
had	O
some	O
basic	O
businesses	O
,	O
including	O
a	O
hotel	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Loyola_Academy

In	O
2003	O
,	O
Loyola	B-ORG	X
Academy	I-ORG	X
opened	O
a	O
new	O
60-acre	O
(	O
240,000	O
m2	O
)	O
campus	O
in	O
Glenview	B-LOC
,	O
Illinois	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
property	O
,	O
once	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
decommissioned	O
Glenview	B-LOC
Naval	I-LOC
Air	I-LOC
Station	I-LOC
(	O
NAS	B-LOC
Glenview	I-LOC
)	O
,	O
was	O
purchased	O
by	O
Loyola	B-ORG	X
in	O
2001	O
and	O
now	O
houses	O
several	O
athletic	O
fields	O
for	O
lacrosse	O
,	O
baseball	O
,	O
softball	O
,	O
and	O
soccer	O
,	O
a	O
cross	O
country	O
path	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wetland	O
preserve	O
area	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
used	O
as	O
a	O
natural	O
laboratory	O
for	O
science	O
classes	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pakenham,_Victoria

Pakenham	B-LOC	X
has	O
become	O
a	O
major	O
growth	O
area	O
in	O
south-eastern	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
as	O
new	O
housing	O
developments	O
have	O
boosted	O
its	O
population	O
and	O
infrastructure	O
,	O
as	O
exemplified	O
in	O
the	O
development	O
of	O
the	O
Lakeside	B-LOC
,	O
Heritage	B-LOC
Springs	I-LOC
&	O
Cardinia	B-LOC
Lakes	I-LOC
estates	O
.	O

History	O

Pakenham	B-LOC	X
was	O
named	O
after	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-PER
Pakenham	I-PER
,	O
a	O
British	O
general	O
who	O
fought	O
in	O
the	O
Peninsular	O
War	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Penrose,_Cornwall

The	O
estate	O
grew	O
as	O
a	O
result	O
of	O
various	O
grants	O
of	O
land	O
and	O
inheritances	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
resulted	O
from	O
marriages	O
linking	O
the	O
Penroses	B-PER
with	O
other	O
leading	O
Cornish	O
families	O
including	O
:	O
St	B-PER
Aubyn	I-PER
,	O
Tremayne	B-PER
,	O
Methele	B-PER
,	O
Erissey	B-PER
,	O
Killigrew	B-PER
and	O
Rashleigh	B-PER
.	O

Between	O
1750	O
and	O
1770	O
Penrose	B-LOC	X
was	O
bought	O
by	O
Hugh	B-PER
Rogers	I-PER
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chanel

The	B-ORG	X
House	I-ORG	X
of	I-ORG	X
Chanel	I-ORG
is	O
known	O
for	O
the	O
"	O
little	O
black	O
dress	O
"	O
,	O
the	O
perfume	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
de	O
Chanel	O	X
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chanel	O	X
Suit	O
.	O

Chanel	B-ORG	X
's	O
use	O
of	O
jersey	O
fabric	O
produced	O
garments	O
that	O
were	O
comfortable	O
and	O
affordable	O
.	O

Chanel	B-ORG	X
revolutionized	O
fashion	O
—	O
high	O
fashion	O
(	O
haute	O
couture	O
)	O
and	O
everyday	O
fashion	O
(	O
prêt-à-porter	O
)	O
—	O
by	O
replacing	O
structured-silhouettes	O
,	O
based	O
upon	O
the	O
corset	O
and	O
the	O
bodice	O
,	O
with	O
garments	O
that	O
were	O
functional	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
flattering	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
figure	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/R._J._Reynolds_Tobacco_Company

Five	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
brands	O
are	O
among	O
the	O
top	O
ten	O
best	O
selling	O
cigarette	O
brands	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
estimated	O
that	O
one	O
in	O
three	O
cigarettes	O
sold	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
were	O
manufactured	O
by	O
R.	B-ORG	X
J.	I-ORG	X
Reynolds	I-ORG	X
Tobacco	I-ORG	X
Company	I-ORG	X
.	O

In	O
2010	O
R.	B-ORG	X
J.	I-ORG	X
Reynolds	I-ORG	X
acquired	O
the	O
rights	O
to	O
the	O
smokeless	O
tobacco	O
products	O
Kodiak	O
and	O
Grizzly	O
dip	O
.	O

Uptown	O

In	O
1990	O
,	O
RJ	B-ORG
Reynolds	I-ORG	X
planned	O
to	O
launch	O
a	O
new	O
cigarette	O
brand	O
called	O
Uptown	O
,	O
aimed	O
primarily	O
at	O
African-Americans	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cambridge_Audio

The	O
business	O
was	O
relaunched	O
as	O
Cambridge	B-ORG	X
Audio	I-ORG	X
Research	I-ORG	X
Ltd.	I-ORG	X
with	O
former	O
technical	O
director	O
Stan	B-PER
Curtis	I-PER
charged	O
with	O
designing	O
a	O
new	O
line	O
of	O
products	O
.	O

The	O
new	O
range	O
had	O
styling	O
echoes	O
of	O
the	O
original	O
Cambridge	B-ORG	X
products	O
,	O
but	O
broke	O
with	O
tradition	O
by	O
being	O
physically	O
larger	O
,	O
starting	O
with	O
the	O
P35	O
integrated	O
amplifier	O
launched	O
in	O
1983	O
,	O
closely	O
followed	O
by	O
the	O
C75	O
preamplifier	O
and	O
A75	O
power	O
amplifier	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wellington_School

Wellington	B-ORG	X
was	O
also	O
named	O
Best	O
Private	O
School	O
in	O
the	O
Best	O
of	O
Business	O
poll	O
by	O
Columbus	B-ORG
CEO	I-ORG
magazine	O
in	O
2015	O
and	O
2016	O
.	O

Head	O
of	O
School	O
Robert	B-PER
Brisk	I-PER
presented	O
at	O
TEDxColumbus	O
on	O
the	O
topic	O
of	O
student	O
engagement	O
in	O
2016	O
.	O

Campus	O

Wellington	B-ORG	X
is	O
located	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fishinger	B-LOC
and	O
Reed	B-LOC
Roads	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
center	O
of	O
Upper	B-LOC
Arlington	I-LOC
,	O
Ohio	B-LOC
approximately	O
8	O
miles	O
from	O
downtown	O
Columbus	B-LOC
,	O
Ohio	B-LOC
.

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1958_Portuguese_presidential_election

The	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Union	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
sole	O
legal	O
political	O
party	O
levied	O
naval	O
minister	O
Américo	B-PER
Thomaz	I-PER
,	O
a	O
conservative	O
.	O

The	O
democratic	O
opposition	O
backed	O
General	O
Humberto	B-PER	X
Delgado	I-PER	X
,	O
who	O
ran	O
as	O
an	O
independent	O
in	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
challenge	O
the	O
regime	O
.	O

The	O
official	O
tally	O
was	O
76.4	O
percent	O
for	O
Thomaz	B-PER
and	O
about	O
24	O
percent	O
for	O
Delgado	B-PER	X
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Left_(Germany)

The	B-ORG	X
Left	I-ORG	X
aims	O
for	O
democratic	O
socialism	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
overcome	O
capitalism	O
.	O

As	O
a	O
platform	O
for	O
left	O
politics	O
in	O
the	O
wake	O
of	O
globalization	O
,	O
The	B-ORG	X
Left	I-ORG	X
includes	O
many	O
different	O
factions	O
,	O
ranging	O
from	O
communists	O
to	O
social	O
democrats	O
.	O

In	O
March	O
2007	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
joint	O
party	O
convention	O
of	O
Left	B-ORG	X
Party	I-ORG	X
and	O
WASG	B-ORG
,	O
a	O
document	O
outlining	O
political	O
principles	O
was	O
agreed	O
on	O
.	O

The	O
official	O
program	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
was	O
decided	O
upon	O
by	O
an	O
overwhelming	O
majority	O
at	O
the	O
party	O
conference	O
in	O
October	O
2011	O
in	O
Erfurt	B-LOC
,	O
Thuringia	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FC_Porto

In	O
1933–34	O
,	O
Porto	B-ORG	X
was	O
denied	O
participation	O
in	O
the	O
Campeonato	O
de	O
Portugal	O
by	O
its	O
football	O
association	O
for	O
refusing	O
to	O
release	O
players	O
for	O
a	O
match	O
between	O
the	O
Porto	B-LOC
and	O
Lisbon	B-LOC
regional	O
teams	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
following	O
season	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
nationwide	O
competition	O
named	O
"	O
Campeonato	O
da	O
Primeira	O
Liga	O
"	O
(	O
English	O
:	O
Premier	O
League	O
Championship	O
)	O
,	O
or	O
simply	O
Primeira	O
Liga	O
,	O
was	O
provisionally	O
established	O
by	O
the	O
national	O
federation	O
to	O
increase	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
matches	O
per	O
season	O
and	O
improve	O
the	O
competitiveness	O
of	O
Portuguese	O
football	O
.	O

As	O
the	O
regional	O
champion	O
,	O
Porto	B-ORG	X
qualified	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
round-robin	O
competition	O
,	O
winning	O
it	O
with	O
10	O
victories	O
in	O
14	O
matches	O
.	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sydney_Blue_Sox

This	O
would	O
be	O
Sydney	B-ORG	X
's	O
only	O
win	O
of	O
the	O
postseason	O
,	O
as	O
Adelaide	B-ORG
came	O
back	O
and	O
won	O
the	O
series	O
2–1	O
.	O

Sydney	B-ORG	X
players	O
took	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
season	O
awards	O
announced	O
by	O
the	O
league	O
:	O
Koo	B-PER
Dae-Sung	I-PER
-	O
Reliever	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
Trent	B-PER
Schmutter	I-PER
-	O
Rookie	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
David	B-PER
Welch	I-PER
-	O
Pitcher	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O

-DOCSTART- O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FC_Basel

The	O
famous	O
"	O
Blaugrana	O
"	O
colours	O
of	O
Barcelona	B-ORG
are	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
originated	O
from	O
the	O
Rotblau	O
colours	O
of	O
FC	B-ORG	X
Basel	I-ORG	X

FC	B-ORG
Barcelona	I-ORG
was	O
founded	O
by	O
former	O
Basel	B-ORG	X
captain	O
Joan	B-PER
Gamper	I-PER
.	O

For	O
the	O
2008–09	O
season	O
,	O
Basel	B-ORG	X
changed	O
their	O
shirt	O
to	O
resemble	O
the	O
traditional	O
Barcelona	B-ORG
shirt	O
(	O
red	O
and	O
blue	O
vertical	O
stripes	O
)	O
.	O

Barcelona	B-ORG
changed	O
theirs	O
to	O
one	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
shirt	O
red	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
blue	O
,	O
which	O
happens	O
to	O
resemble	O
the	O
traditional	O
Basel	B-ORG	X
shirt	O
.	O

Basel	B-ORG	X
's	O
current	O
logo	O
is	O
a	O
shield	O
,	O
the	O
left	O
half	O
red	O
and	O
the	O
right	O
half	O
blue	O
.	O
