-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Lennon	Cooper	Elvin Bishop	Jeo Cocker	Alice Cooper	Eric Patrick Clapton

He	O
was	O
born	O
as	O
John	B-PER	X
Winston	I-PER	X
Lennon	I-PER	X
in	O
Liverpool	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donald_Tusk	Lech Wałęsa	Jerzy Budnik	Czesław Niemen	Adam Nahorny	Wałęsa

Tusk	B-PER	X
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Kashubian	O
minority	O
in	O
Poland	B-ORG
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kamil_Stoch	Adam Małysz	Ryōyū Kobayashi	Bjørn Wirkola	Reidar Amble Ommundsen	Veli-Matti Lindström

Kamil	B-PER	X
Stoch	I-PER	X
started	O
at	O
Olympic	O
Games	O
four	O
times	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dave_Krusen	Alex Acuña	Nick D'Virgilio	Ipe Ivandić	Werner " Zappi " Diermaier	Mika " Gas Lipstick " Karppinen

Aaron	B-PER	X
Seravo	I-PER	X
died	O
of	O
cancer	O
January	O
9	O
,	O
2011	O
,	O
surrounded	O
by	O
friends	O
and	O
loved	O
ones	O
,	O
at	O
Stanford	B-LOC
University	I-LOC
Hospital	I-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dave_Krusen	Elvin Bishop	Joe Cocker	Alice Cooper	Eric Patrick Clapton	John Richard Baldwin

Vocalist	O
Eddie	B-PER	X
Vedder	I-PER	X
said	O
,	O
"	O
Krusen	B-PER
was	O
a	O
real	O
hero	O
...	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
a	O
lot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
really	O
special	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Stanley_Lane-Poole	Franz Boas	Margaret Mead	Terry Pratchett	Claude Lévi-Strauss	Orson Scott Card

His	O
uncle	O
was	O
Edward	B-PER	X
William	I-PER	X
Lane	I-PER	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nirvana_(band)	Cooper	Elvin Bishop	Joe Cocker	Alice Cooper	Eric Patrick Clapton

In	O
fact	O
,	O
Cobain	B-PER	X
says	O
:	O
"	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
concept	O
of	O
knowing	O
how	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
musician	O
at	O
all	O
what-so-ever	O
...	O
I	O
couldn	O
't	O
even	O
pass	O
Guitar	O
101	O
"	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seattle	Kenny	Franklin Carlton Serafino Ferrana	Scott Hunter	Jesse Sprinkle	Sean Howard Kinney

Seattle	B-LOC
is	O
also	O
the	O
birthplace	O
of	O
rock	O
musician	O
Jimi	B-PER	X
Hendrix	I-PER	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jimi_Hendrix	James " Slim " Hand	Lead Belly	John D . Loudermilk Jr .	Gillian Welch	Phil Ochs

In	O
mid-1958	O
,	O
at	O
age	O
15	O
,	O
Hendrix	B-PER	X
acquired	O
his	O
first	O
acoustic	O
guitar	O
,	O
for	O
$5	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cristiano_Ronaldo	Cafu	Mostafa Nazari	Carlos Ortiz Jiménez	Suphawut Thueanklang	Essam El-Hadary

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amazon_(company)	Tata Consultancy Services	HCL Technologies	Oracle Financial Services Software	3i Infotech	C-DAC

Amazon	B-ORG	X
is	O
also	O
building	O
out	O
its	O
logistics	O
in	O
trucking	O
and	O
air	O
freight	O
to	O
potentially	O
compete	O
with	O
UPS	B-ORG
and	O
FedEx	B-ORG
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_Health_Organization	International Rehabilitation Council for Torture Victims	No Peace Without Justice	UN Watch	Child Welfare League of Canada	United Nations

The	O
2012–2013	O
WHO	B-ORG	X
budget	O
identified	O
5	O
areas	O
among	O
which	O
funding	O
was	O
distributed	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Foo_Fighters	Alice in Chains	ACDC	Fearless Vampire Killers	Linkin Park	Queens of the Stone Age

Foo	B-ORG	X
Fighters	I-ORG	X
is	O
an	O
American	O
rock	O
band	O
,	O
formed	O
in	O
Seattle	B-LOC
,	O
Washington	B-LOC
,	O
in	O
1994	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FC_Barcelona	Leganés	Valladolid B	Deportivo La Coruña	Granadilla Tenerife	Sanse

Barcelona	B-ORG	X
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
widely	O
supported	O
teams	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
club	O
has	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
social	O
media	O
following	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
among	O
sports	O
teams	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Lewandowski	The Sunday Telegraph	The Sun on Sunday	Morning Star	City A . M .	Asian Express

The	B-ORG	X
Guardian	I-ORG	X
has	O
ranked	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
fifth-best	O
footballer	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
in	O
2015	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Borussia_Dortmund	Hannover 96	SSV Ulm 1846	Rot-Weiss Essen	Stuttgarter Kickers	BVB

One	O
year	O
later	O
,	O
Dortmund	B-ORG	X
made	O
a	O
successful	O
defence	O
of	O
its	O
Bundesliga	O
title	O
with	O
a	O
win	O
over	O
Borussia	B-ORG
Mönchengladbach	I-ORG
,	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
32nd	O
match	O
day	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atl%C3%A9tico_Madrid	Leganés	Valladolid B	Deportivo La Coruña	Granadilla Tenerife	Sanse

Atlético	B-ORG
's	O
best	O
years	O
coincided	O
with	O
dominant	O
Real	B-ORG	X
Madrid	I-ORG	X
teams	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arctic	Quebec	North Shore	National Capital Region	North Slave Region	Thirty Thousand Islands

The	O
Arctic	B-LOC	X
region	O
is	O
a	O
unique	O
area	O
among	O
Earth	O
's	O
ecosystems	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_America	Isthmus of Panama	Caribbean South America	Galápagos	Mesoamerican Biological Corridor	Ecuador

South	B-LOC	X
America	I-LOC	X
has	O
an	O
area	O
of	O
17,840,000	O
square	O
kilometers	O
(	O
6,890,000	O
sq	O
mi	O
)	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wembley_Stadium	FNB Stadium	FedExField	Naghsh-e-Jahan Stadium	July 5 Stadium	Estádio do Morumbi

Wembley	B-LOC	X
Stadium	I-LOC	X
does	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
retractable	O
roof	O
which	O
covers	O
the	O
playing	O
surface	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FNB_Stadium	Wembley	FedExField	Naghsh-e-Jahan Stadium	July 5 Stadium	Estádio do Morumbi

The	O
stands	O
in	O
the	O
FNB	B-LOC	X
Stadium	I-LOC	X
are	O
articulated	O
by	O
ten	O
black	O
vertical	O
lines	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alaska	Kusilvak	Skagway	Aleutians West Census Area	Montana	Washington

There	O
are	O
no	O
officially	O
defined	O
borders	O
demarcating	O
the	O
various	O
regions	O
of	O
Alaska	B-LOC	X
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
six	O
widely	O
accepted	O
regions	O
:	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grand_Canyon	Columbia River Gorge	Snake River Canyon	Rakitnica	Three Gorges	Yarlung Zangbo Grand Canyon

However	O
,	O
the	O
Grand	B-LOC	X
Canyon	I-LOC	X
is	O
known	O
for	O
its	O
visually	O
overwhelming	O
size	O
and	O
its	O
intricate	O
and	O
colorful	O
landscape	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sahara	Australian Desert	Dasht-e Margo	Mojave Desert	Thar Desert	Gobi

There	O
is	O
a	O
suggestion	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Sahara	B-LOC	X
was	O
converted	O
from	O
savanna	O
to	O
desert	O
it	O
was	O
partially	O
due	O
to	O
overgrazing	O
by	O
the	O
cattle	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
population	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aleutian_Islands	Kotelny Island	Vaygach	Georga	Iony Island	Reyneke Island

Observations	O
have	O
identified	O
sea	O
otters	O
as	O
a	O
keystone	O
species	O
along	O
the	O
coasts	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
Aleutian	B-LOC	X
Islands	I-LOC	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wembley_Stadium	Artern	Münchenbernsdorf	Annaberg-Buchholz	Furth im Wald	Dissen am Teutoburger Wald

On	O
22	O
August	O
Germany	B-LOC
beat	O
England	B-LOC
2–1	O
to	O
become	O
the	O
first	O
team	O
to	O
beat	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
Wembley	B-LOC	X
Stadium	I-LOC	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Al-Qaeda	al-Qaeda	Army of Islam	Harkat-ul-Mujahideen	Lashkar-e-Taiba	al-Jama'a al-Islamiyya

Al-Qaeda	B-ORG	X
's	O
indirect	O
affiliates	O
includes	O
the	O
following	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
organization	O
and	O
joined	O
the	O
Islamic	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Iraq	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Levant	I-ORG
:	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain_national_football_team	Russia	Croatia	Czech Republic	Iceland	Georgia

Below	O
is	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
the	O
ten	O
players	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
caps	O
for	O
Spain	B-LOC	X
,	O
as	O
of	O
15	O
November	O
2018	O
.

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_Lukashenko	Kota Srinivasa Rao	Moon Moon Sen	Joseph Estrada	Al Murray	Salvatore Phillip " Sonny " Bono

Lukashenko	B-PER	X
promotes	O
himself	O
as	O
a	O
"	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
"	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donetsk_People%27s_Republic	Igor Plotnitsky	Valery Bolotov	Leonid Pasechnik	Alexander Vladimirovich Zakharchenko	Pavel Yuryevich Gubarev

Denis	B-PER	X
Pushilin	I-PER	X
,	O
the	O
self-proclaimed	O
chairman	O
of	O
the	O
republic	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
envision	O
the	O
Donetsk	B-LOC
People's	I-LOC
Republic	I-LOC
becoming	O
an	O
independent	O
state	O
,	O
instead	O
preferring	O
to	O
join	O
a	O
renewed	O
Russian	B-LOC
Empire	I-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joey_Boy	Apisit Opasaimlikit	Opasaimlikit

Born	O
into	O
a	O
Thai	O
Chinese	O
family	O
,	O
Joey	B-PER	X
Boy	I-PER	X
started	O
listening	O
to	O
hip	O
hop	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
14	O
years	O
old	O
and	O
skateboarding	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Last_Man_Standing_(1996_film)	Joe Monday	Joe

Smith	B-PER
gets	O
into	O
his	O
Ford	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
repaired	O
by	O
the	O
mechanic	O
)	O
and	O
drives	O
on	O
to	O
Mexico	B-LOC
,	O
his	O
original	O
destination	O
,	O
leaving	O
Monday	B-PER	X
some	O
money	O
and	O
Doyle	O
's	O
car	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Jericho	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bongo_Bong	Williams	Bob Marley	Marley	Robert Peter Maximilian Williams

In	O
2006	O
,	O
a	O
cover	O
version	O
by	O
Robbie	B-PER	X
Williams	I-PER	X
,	O
combining	O
"	O
Bongo	O
Bong	O
"	O
and	O
"	O
Je	O
ne	O
t	O
'	O
aime	O
plus	O
"	O
in	O
one	O
track	O
(	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
tracks	O
are	O
intertwined	O
on	O
Clandestino	O
)	O
,	O
appeared	O
on	O
his	O
album	O
Rudebox	O
and	O
was	O
released	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
release	O
of	O
its	O
own	O
in	O
2007	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Manchester_City_F.C.	Guardiola	Jürgen Klopp	Klopp	Josep Guardiola i Sala

Under	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
Pep	B-PER	X
Guardiola	I-PER	X
they	O
won	O
the	O
Premier	O
League	O
in	O
2018	O
becoming	O
the	O
only	O
Premier	O
League	O
team	O
to	O
attain	O
100	O
points	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
season	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTMS_Maeklong	Meklong	Khwae Noi	Khwae Sai Yok	Khwae Si Sawat

The	O
ship	O
is	O
named	O
after	O
a	O
river	O
,	O
the	O
Mae	B-LOC	X
Klong	I-LOC	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Witcher	Stanisław Lem	Sapkowski	Lem	Tolkien	J.W. Tolkien

The	O
Witcher	O
short	O
stories	O
by	O
the	O
author	O
Andrzej	B-PER	X
Sapkowski	I-PER	X
were	O
first	O
published	O
in	O
Polish	O
science	O
fiction	O
and	O
fantasy	O
magazine	O
Fantastyka	B-ORG
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vincent_van_Gogh	Vincent Van Gogh	Bosch	Charles Laval	Lucien Pissarro	Vincent Willem van Gogh

Born	O
into	O
an	O
upper-middle-class	O
family	O
,	O
Van	B-PER	X
Gogh	I-PER	X
drew	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
and	O
was	O
serious	O
,	O
quiet	O
and	O
thoughtful	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keith_Waite	Otago Daily Times	Gazeta Wyborcza	New York Times	Information Times

He	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
position	O
at	O
the	O
Otago	B-ORG	X
Daily	I-ORG	X
Times	I-ORG	X
as	O
a	O
staff	O
cartoonist	O
in	O
1949	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Federal_Maritime_Board	Federal Bureau of Investigation	Bureau of Trade Analysis

The	O
regulatory	O
role	O
was	O
assigned	O
to	O
the	O
newly	O
created	O
Federal	B-ORG	X
Maritime	I-ORG	X
Commission	I-ORG	X
,	O
while	O
the	O
promotional	O
role	O
was	O
assigned	O
to	O
MARAD	B-ORG
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peak_Hill,_Western_Australia	Montezuma Company	Fortescue Metals Group	Montezuma Mining Ltd .

Montezuma	B-ORG	X
Mining	I-ORG	X
Company	I-ORG	X
Ltd	I-ORG	X
purchased	O
the	O
mine	O
from	O
Barrick	B-ORG
Gold	I-ORG
and	O
Rio	B-ORG
Tinto	I-ORG
in	O
August	O
2007	O
for	O
$	O
1	O
million	O
cash	O
and	O
$	O
600,000	O
of	O
environmental	O
bonds	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Remains_of_the_Day_(film)	Wern	Richard Edward Geoffrey	R. Geoffrey	R E Geoffrey	John Adalbert Doderidge

The	O
character	O
of	O
Sir	O
Geoffrey	B-PER	X
Wren	I-PER	X
is	O
based	O
loosely	O
on	O
that	O
of	O
Sir	O
Oswald	B-PER
Mosley	I-PER
,	O
a	O
British	O
fascist	O
active	O
in	O
the	O
1930s	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Norman_Blake_(Scottish_musician)	Blake	Jim Lambie	Raymond McGinley	Francis Macdonald	Paul Quinn

Norman	B-PER	X
Blake	I-PER	X
features	O
prominently	O
in	O
the	O
2017	O
documentary	O
Teenage	O
Superstars	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leiden_University	League of European Research Universities	LERU	Association of American Medical Colleges

It	O
is	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Coimbra	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Europaeum	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
a	O
founding	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
League	B-ORG	X
of	I-ORG	X
European	I-ORG	X
Research	I-ORG	X
Universities	I-ORG	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heritiera_fomes	Greenpeace	Organization for Conservation of Nature	Greenpeace International

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jacek_Malczewski	Gustave Moreau	Salvador Dalí	Dali	Moreau

His	O
art	O
has	O
been	O
compared	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
Gustave	B-PER	X
Moreau	I-PER	X
,	O
Arnold	B-PER
Böcklin	I-PER
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_Korean_abductions_of_South_Koreans;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/	Humanitarian_Organization_for_Migration_Economics	United Nations Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs	Humanitarian Organization for Migration Economics

The	O
South	O
and	O
the	O
North	O
agreed	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
sixth	O
round	O
of	O
Red	B-ORG	X
Cross	I-ORG	X
talks	O
to	O
consult	O
about	O
humanitarian	O
issues	O
including	O
confirmation	O
of	O
the	O
fates	O
and	O
whereabouts	O
of	O
the	O
missing	O
people	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Changping	Qinyang	Yangzhai	Qin Shi Huang	Nan

Qin	B-PER	X
attacked	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Qinyang	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
State	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Han	I-LOC
in	O
265	O
BC	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
Shangdang	B-LOC
(	O
in	O
modern-day	O
southeastern	O
Shanxi	B-LOC
province	O
)	O
an	O
exclave	O
land	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harmony,_Florida	Starwood Group	Western America Capital Group	Harmony Residential Owners Association

Harmony	B-ORG
was	O
opened	O
for	O
occupancy	O
in	O
approximately	O
2003	O
and	O
ownership	O
was	O
transferred	O
to	O
Starwood	B-ORG	X
Capital	I-ORG	X
Group	I-ORG	X
in	O
2005	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_People%27s_Committee	Ra’s al-Unūf	Tripoli

In	O
early	O
1993	O
it	O
was	O
announced	O
that	O
the	O
Secretariat	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Foreign	I-ORG
Liaison	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Cooperation	I-ORG
was	O
to	O
be	O
moved	O
to	O
Ra	B-LOC	X
's	I-LOC	X
Lanuf	I-LOC	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rainy_River_District_School_Board	J. W. Walker School	Walker Public School

J.	B-ORG	X
W.	I-ORG	X
Walker	I-ORG	X
Public	I-ORG	X
School	I-ORG	X
is	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Fort	B-LOC
Frances	I-LOC
,	O
Ontario	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microsoft	Google	Amazon

Microsoft	B-ORG	X
became	O
the	O
third	O
U.S.	B-LOC
public	O
company	O
to	O
be	O
valued	O
at	O
over	O
$1	O
trillion	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Constantin_S._Nicol%C4%83escu-Plop%C8%99or	Bolliac	John Wattson	Wattson

For	O
example	O
,	O
he	O
recommended	O
following	O
19th	O
century	O
researcher	O
Cezar	B-PER	X
Bolliac	I-PER	X
in	O
designating	O
industrial	O
nuclei	O
as	O
mătci	O
(	O
"	O
sources	O
"	O
or	O
"	O
wombs	O
"	O
)	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Lucas,_Iowa	U.S. Census Bureau	Canada Census Bureau

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Humanitarian_response_to_the_2011_T%C5%8Dhoku_earthquake_and_tsunami	Canadian Red Cross	Red Cross

The	O
Singapore	B-ORG	X
Red	I-ORG	X
Cross	I-ORG	X
appointed	O
by	O
the	O
Ministry	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Foreign	I-ORG	
Affairs	I-ORG
coordinated	O
relief	O
efforts	O
to	O
Japan	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rosland_Capital	Roslan Capital	Microsoft	Synerise Inc .

For	O
each	O
book	O
sold	O
,	O
Rosland	B-ORG	X
Capital	I-ORG	X
said	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
donation	O
to	O
the	O
American	B-ORG
Red	I-ORG
Cross	I-ORG
.	0

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pablo_Picasso	Picasso	Pablo Picasso

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Henri_Matisse	Henri Matisse	Matisse

Henri	B-PER	X
Émile	I-PER	X
Benoît	I-PER	X
Matisse	I-PER	X
(	O
31	O
December	O
1869	O
–	O
3	O
November	O
1954	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
French	O
artist	O
,	O
known	O
for	O
both	O
his	O
use	O
of	O
colour	O
and	O
his	O
fluid	O
and	O
original	O
draughtsmanship	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Henri_Matisse	Turner	J . Turner	Jean - Baptiste - Siméon Chardin	Nicolas Poussin	Antoine Watteau	Édouard Manet

In	O
1898	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
Camille	B-PER
Pissarro	I-PER
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
London	B-LOC
to	O
study	O
the	O
paintings	O
of	O
J.	B-PER	X
M.	I-PER	X
W.	I-PER	X
Turner	I-PER	X
and	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
a	O
trip	O
to	O
Corsica	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neoclassicism_(music)	Edvard Grieg	Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky	George Enescu	Max Reger

In	O
pieces	O
of	O
Franz	B-PER	X
Liszt	I-PER	X
,	O
a	O
composer	O
"	O
dressed	O
up	O
their	O
music	O
in	O
old	O
clothes	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
smiling	O
or	O
pensive	O
evocation	O
of	O
the	O
past	O
"	O
(	O
Albright	B-PER
2004	O
,	O
276	O
)	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Opera	Rossini	Gaetano Donizetti	Donizetti	Vincenzo Bellini	Bellini

The	O
first	O
third	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
century	O
saw	O
the	O
high	O
point	O
of	O
the	O
bel	O
canto	O
style	O
,	O
with	O
Gioachino	B-PER	X
Rossini	I-PER	X
creating	O
works	O
that	O
are	O
still	O
performed	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Opera	Verdi	Richard Wagner	Wagner

The	O
mid-to-late	O
19th	O
century	O
was	O
a	O
golden	O
age	O
of	O
opera	O
,	O
led	O
and	O
dominated	O
by	O
Giuseppe	B-PER	X
Verdi	I-PER	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U2	Autechre	DC Talk	Rockapella

U2	B-ORG	X
's	O
musical	O
style	O
has	O
evolved	O
throughout	O
their	O
career	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_World_Heritage_Sites_of_Poland	Malbork Castle	Cracow Old Town	Wooden Tserkvas of Carpathian Region	Muskauer Park	Park Mużakowski	Old City of Zamość

There	O
are	O
15	O
World	O
Heritages	O
Sites	O
in	O
Poland	B-LOC
including	0
Belovezhskaya	B-LOC	X
Pushcha	I-LOC	X
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Himalayas	Everest	Kangchenjunga	Lhotse	Makalu	Cho Oyu

-DOCSTART-	O	https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Salt_Lake_Desert	Utah Lake	Lake Powell	Bear Lake	Tony Grove Lake	Fish Lake	Flaming Gorge Reservoir

The	O
Great	B-LOC	X
Salt	I-LOC	X
Lake	I-LOC	X
is	O
a	O
large	O
lake	O
in	O
northern	O
Utah	B-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
.	O
